

Mykola Baran

Web Developer



akaroot@akaroot.pro (mailto:akaroot@akaroot.pro)



Ternopil,, UA

ABOUT

I'm a full stack web developer who loves working with open source technology. I work best at planning the architecture of web applications and their development life cycles. I also love to get the community involved and have had much experience with building and organizing large open source groups.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, PrivatBank (http://pb.ua)

Jun 2011 - Present ② 3 years 11 months

- Created management system for corporate linux OS
- iOS MDM System
- DHCP web-based management service
- Service for monitoring network printers

PHP Developer, PrivatBank (http://pb.ua)

Oct 2009 - Jun 2011 ② 1 year 8 months

- Created system for utility bills
- Created monitoring service for Puppet
- Created services for logistics
- Maintained servers

Laboratory Assistant, Ternopil National Pedagogical University (http://tnpu.edu.ua)

Aug 2008 - Oct 2009 **②** 1 year 2 months

- Created Moodle module for managing academic groups
- Maintained servers
- Support learning system Moodle

System Administrator, Ternopil National Pedagogical University (http://tnpu.edu.ua)

Dec 2006 - Sep 2008 ② 1 year 9 months

Created Moodle module for managing academic groups

- Maintained servers
- Support learning system Moodle

SKILLS

Frontend (): HTML, CSS, Javascript.

Backend (): PHP, Ruby, Python, Node, Go.

Databases (): MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.

Other (): Git, Linux, Apache, Nginx, DHCP.

EDUCATION

computer engineering, M.S. degree, Ternopil National Pedagogical University Sep 2004 - Jul 2009

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian (Native speaker), English (Pre-Intermediate), Russian (Near native).